pikimal.com 2013-12-18

# Privacy Policy | Pikimal

## Pikimal Privacy Policy

Last updated June 1st, 2012

WebKite provides the functionality for the web site hosted at pikimal.com (the "Site") and related services (the "Services") to enable our clients to easily build data-driven sites, to build an understanding of language, and to create fact and data-driven web-sites which enable people to make better decisions. WebKite values the privacy of the users, subscribers, publishers, members, and others who visit the Site or Services (collectively or individually, "Users"). In the normal course of business these facts may be shared, without limitation, with the licensee of WebKite and the operator of this site. By using the Site or Services, you expressly consent to the information handling practices described in this notice. This Privacy Notice is subject to the Pikimal Terms of Service. Your use of the Site and Services are subject at all times to this Privacy Notice and the Terms of Service.

## The Information Pikimal Collects

In order to use the Site or Services, users may register with the site and in the process we may collect certain user-provided, personally identifiable information including name and email address. Our server logs automatically collected information, such as your IP address, pages you access, your browser type and language, and the date and time of your visit, which helps us track users' movements around our site and understand trends.

We may assign your computer one or more cookies which may collect information to facilitate access to our website and to personalize your online experience. We may use standard Internet tools, such web beacons, which collect information that tracks your use of our website and enables us to customize our services and advertisements.

We allow registered users to send invitations to their friends. We use your friends' email addresses to send them these invitations, and we retain their addresses for the purpose of identifying them when they come to our site. Unless they register with the site, we do not send them any other emails or use their email address for any other purpose.

## The Way Pikimal Uses Information

Pikimal uses the information that you provide or that we collect to operate, maintain, enhance, and provide all of the features and services found on the Site and Services as well as to track user-generated content and Users to the extent necessary to comply as a service provider with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act.

We will use your email address, without further consent, for administrative communications such as notifying you of major Site and Services updates, for customer service purposes, to address copyright infringement or defamation issues, or to contact you regarding any content that you have posted to or downloaded from the Site or Services.

Pikimal uses all of the information that we collect to understand the usage trends and preferences of our Users, to improve the way the Site or Services works and looks, and to create new features and functionality.

Pikimal may use Automatically Collected information and Cookies information to: (a) automatically update the Pikimal application on your system; (b) remember your information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you access the Pikimal Platform; (c) monitor aggregate site usage metrics such as total number of visitors and pages accessed; (d) provide such metrics to Users as they pertain to such User uploaded content; (e) track your entries, submissions, and status in any promotions or other activities.

## When Pikimal Discloses Information

Pikimal does not share your information with other organizations for their marketing or promotional uses without your prior express consent. Please be aware, however, that any information that you voluntarily choose to display on the Site or Services such as when you publish attribution credits for documents or profile information becomes publicly available and may be collected and used by others without restriction.

We may disclose aggregate information about our users to researchers, product developers, other organizations, or publicly. This information will not personally identify you, but it may be possible to use this information in combination with your site activity to identify how your user has utilized the site.

We may disclose User information to affiliated companies or other businesses or persons to: provide web site hosting, maintenance, and security services; fulfill orders; conduct data analysis; create industry reports for research and/or profit; assist in product feature development; offer certain functionality; and assist Pikimal in improving the Site or Services and creating new services features. We require that these parties process such information in compliance with this Privacy Notice, we authorize only a limited use of such information, and we require these parties to use reasonable confidentiality measures.

Pikimal may disclose User information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with state and federal laws (such as U.S. Copyright law) or respond to a court order, judicial or other government subpoena, or warrant in the manner required by the requesting entity.

Pikimal also reserves the right to disclose User information that we believe, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary: to take precautions against liability; to protect Pikimal from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful uses; to investigate and defend ourselves against third-party claims or allegations; to assist government enforcement agencies; to protect the security or integrity of the Site and Services; or to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Pikimal, our Users, or others.

## Your Choices

You may, of course, decline to share your personally identifiable information with Pikimal, in which case Pikimal will not be able to provide to you some of the features and functionality found on the Site or Services. You may update or correct your user information and preferences at any time by contacting us.

You may delete your account in its entirety at any point; however, any information we have previously collected from you will not be deleted.

To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting you account access or making corrections to your information. YOU ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR MAINTAINING THE SECRECY OF YOUR UNIQUE PASSWORD AND ACCOUNT INFORMATION AT ALL TIMES.

Any personal information that you disclose on public areas of the site (item discussions, message boards, profile descriptions, blog comments, etc.) becomes publicly available and could be collected and used by anyone on the Internet. We recommend that you do not provide any sensitive or personally identifiable information when contributing to such public content.

## Third Party Affiliates

Information shared through Facebook Connect is subject to the same privacy agreement as other user information collected through pikimal.com. By agreeing to the "Request for Permission" through Facebook Connect, you grant us permission to access your private profile information, including, but not limited to: email address, name, birthday, status updates, photos, notes, "likes", and education/work history. This data cannot and will not be collected unless you voluntarily choose to allow pikimal.com access.

In the future we may have third-party sites (retail or otherwise) affiliated with pikimal.com. All transactions through these sites are subject to their privacy agreements.

In the future there may also be third-party sites who use our API. These third parties may have access to your data (which may include personal information) via our API and webservices or arrangements with our business partners. These people may use this information for their own purposes, which may be either commercial or non-commercial in nature.

We also use third party advertisements to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in your internet security software. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites and could include the inability to login to accounts, services or programs.

## Our Commitment to Data Security

Pikimal uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Pikimal, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, Pikimal makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. If Pikimal learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. Pikimal may post a notice on the Site if a security breach occurs. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive a free written notice of a security breach you can notify us.

## Our Commitment to Children's Privacy

If you ARE UNDER 13 YEARS OF age, then please do not use or access the Site or Services at any time or in any manner. Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, Pikimal does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information from persons under 13 years of age. If Pikimal learns that personally identifiable information of persons less than 13 years of age has been collected on or through the Site or Services, then Pikimal will take the appropriate steps to delete this information. If you are the parent or legal guardian of a child under 13 who has registered with the Site or Services, then please contact Pikimal to have that child's account terminated and information deleted.

## International Visitors

For Users visiting the Site or Services from the European Economic Area or other non-U.S. territories, please note that any data you enter into the Site or Services will be transferred outside the European Economic Area or such other non-U.S. territory for use by Pikimal and its affiliates for any of the purposes described herein.In addition, because Pikimal operates globally, we may make information we gather available to worldwide business units and affiliates. By providing any data on the Site or Services, you hereby expressly consent to such transfers of your data to the United States or other countries.

## In the Event of Merger or Sale

In the event that Pikimal is acquired by or merged with a third-party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information that we have collected from Users as part of that merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control.

This Privacy Notice may be revised periodically without further notice to you and this will be reflected by a last modified date above. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. In general, we only use your personal information in the manner described in the Privacy Notice in effect when we received that personal information. Your continued use of the Site or Services constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Notice and any future revisions. For revisions to this Privacy Notice that may be materially less restrictive on our use or disclosure of personal information you have provided to us, we will make reasonable efforts to notify you and obtain your consent before implementing revisions with respect to such information.

## Pikimal Contact Information

Please contact Pikimal LLC with any questions or comments about this Privacy Notice, your personal information, and our third-party disclosure practices or your consent choices at: WebKite, 700 River Ave, Suite 440, Pittsburgh, PA, 15212 or by email. We will respond to your inquiry within 45 days of its receipt.
